[SCOFFS]
Oh, no, he didn't.
So how's it going with Sheldon?
Are you guys still not talking?
(Leonard:)Not only is he still not talking to me,
but he does this thing...
(Leonard:)...where he stares at you
and tries to get your brain to explode.
(Penny:)You know,
like in the classic sci-fi movie Scanners?
Like: Bzz-phew!
(Leonard:)Never mind.
How about this one?
It says, "I know my physics,
but I'm still a fun guy."
(Penny:)Oh.
Oh, I didn't know
they still made corduroy suits.
(Leonard:)They don't. That's why I saved this one.
(Penny:)Okay, well,
let's just see what else you have.
(Penny:)Okay, here.
Take this and this and this...
(Penny:)- ...and these.
- Is this stuff you want me to try on?
(Penny:)No, this is stuff I want you to throw out.
(Penny:)Seriously, don't even give it to charity.
You won't be helping anyone.
What's this?